每人一份意大利蛋饼
Ooh! Individual frittatas!
规格真高 你真幸运 菲尔
What a treat. You're a lucky man, Phil.
-我一直这么说 我... -菲尔
- I'm always saying, I'm... - Phil.
-抱歉 -你又把牛奶放外边了
- Sorry. - You left the milk out again.
我得带一个回家吃
I may have to take one of these little guys home.
克莱尔 你找到我借你的保鲜盒了吗
Claire, did you ever find that Tupperware I lent you?
亲爱的 跟你说过一百遍了
Sweetie, for the hundredth time,
我还给你了 记得吗
I gave it back to you, remember?
我是记得你说过一百遍
I remember you telling me a hundred times,
可我现在都只能用塑料袋盛豌豆汤
yet my pea soup is in baggies.
你检查过车子吗
Did you check your car?
在那个
In the...
后备箱里
Trunk.
上次你就是在那里找到了
Because that's where you found that thing
那个你以为早就给我了的东西
that you thought that you gave me long time ago,
-那个 那个 -披萨刀
- the... the... - Pizza cutter.
-是的 那次是我错了 -就一团塑料而已
- Yes, I was wrong that time. I-- - It's a piece of plastic.
你把早午餐毁了
You're ruining brunch.
别想太多了 小卡
Don't sweat it, Cam.
我也老是忘事儿
I forget things all the time.
比如我就老是记不住
Like I can never remember the name
我喜欢的那个天气播报员的名字
of that weather guy that I liked. Uh...
什么雷 什么风的
Thunder something. Stormy...
闪电风暴 管他叫什么呢
Flash Stormy? Ah, whatever the hell it is.
-我不知道 -吃你的蛋吧 杰
- I don't know. - Mm, just eat your eggs, Jay.
对 吃你的蛋吧 杰
Yeah, just eat your eggs, Jay.
爷爷受到教训了
Grandpa got told!
看他们那样
Look at them.
所有人都觉得莉莉超可爱
They all think Lily's so great.
新鲜感总会消失的
The novelty will wear off.
我们以前才是家里最萌的
We used to be the cute ones.
现在注意力全集中在她身上了
Now she gets all the attention.
我们得灭了她
We need to take her down.
我应该记得他的名字的
And I should remember his name, too,
因为你妈和我为他还大吵了一架
because your mom and I got in a big fight over him.
她那时候开着敞篷车 我跟她说
She was using the convertible, and I told her,
把顶篷升上来 那谁说今晚会下雨的
"Put the top up because it's supposed to rain tonight, according to..."
那人叫 部分·多云
P-p-p-partly McCloudy?
管他叫什么破名呢 反正呢
Whatever the hell his name is. Anyway...
她没照做 车毁了
She didn't. Ruined the car.
我说这话不是因为我总帮我妈说话
Well, not to be the one that always come to mom's defense...
干吗呢 都20年前的事了
What? It was 20 years ago.
怎么了 难道他现在还会关你禁闭啊
What, you think he's gonna ground you?
是你干的
It was you?
是的 是的 是我把顶蓬放下来
Yes. Yes, I left the top down,
让妈妈背了黑锅
and I let mom take the fall.
害得他俩离婚了
And then they got divorced.
-12年以后才离的 -我就这么一说
- 12 years later. - I'm just saying.
你毁了早午餐
Ugh. You're ruining brunch.
放轻松 那都好多年前的事了
Relax. It was years ago.
这种事也有个追诉时效的嘛
There's a statute of limitation on this stuff.
既然这样 我干脆告诉你们
In that case, I should probably let you know
我把顶篷放下来是为了散一下烟味
I let the top down to let out the cigarette smoke.
不是我抽的 不是我
Not--not mine. Not mine.
是我一个坏朋友伊利诺
My--my bad friend Eleanor.
所谓伊利诺其实是她男朋友艾伦
Eleanor being her boyfriend Allen.
追诉时效
Statute of limitations.
放松点 没事的
Oh, relax, it's okay.
记不记得我告诉你们
Remember when I told you
说我不能赶去看你们花样滑冰的半决赛
that I couldn't get to your figure skating semifinal
是因为工作脱不开身
because I was stuck at work?
记得
Yeah.
所谓脱不开身其实是烂醉如泥
Well, by "stuck" I meant "drunk,"
所谓工作 其实是在高尔夫球场
and by "work" I meant "the golf course."
-老爸 不是吧 -我想起来一件事
- Wow. Dad! Oh, no. - I got one. I got one.
记不记得那次我们一块去打高尔夫
Remember that time we went golfing together,
-你一杆进洞来着 -记得啊
- and you got a hole-in-one? - Yeah?
你其实没打出一杆进洞
You never got a hole-in-one.
是我闲着无聊 把球踢进洞里了
I got bored and I kicked it in the hole.
这可真有意思 我来说点更好玩的
This is fun. Here's a corker.
医院以前可不像现在这样给婴儿贴姓名标签牌
They didn't used to label babies as carefully in hospitals,
-在两天之内 -现在不是时候 菲尔
- so for two days-- - Not now, Phil.
你什么意思 是你把球踢进洞里去的
What do you mean, you-- you kicked the ball in the hole?
怎么 当时那球 是在洞边上吗
What, was it, like, on the edge?
是啊 是在那个
Yeah, it was on the edge of that, uh...
那什么 在那沙丘边上
What? That--that sandy thing.
老天 我今天可怎么去面对我的朋友们呢
Gee, it's sure gonna be fun to face my friends today.
你不一定非得告诉他们啊
Well, you don't have to tell them.
他们叫我"高手"呢 米奇
They call me "Ace," Mitch.
我在那地方免费喝了二十年的柠檬水
I haven't paid for a lemonade down there in 20 years.
你生我的气了
You're mad at me?
这下可好 老爸 你毁了早午餐
Great, daddy. You ruined brunch.
确实是
You did!
这事今天得有个了结
This ends today.
能帮点忙吗
A little help here?
米兰达·康奈尔就住在街角
You can't expect me to focus
你怎么能指望我集中精神呢
when Miranda Cornell lives right down your street.
她简直就是包裹在牛仔打底裤里的美梦
She's like a dream wrapped in a wish poured into jeggings.
是的是的 是挺美好的
Yeah, yeah, that's nice and all,
我们还得做个机关呢
but we got a trap to set.
你确定这能有用吗
Are you sure this is going to work?
相信我 我们用饼干作为诱饵
Trust me. We'll use these cookies as bait.
莉莉可爱吃了
Lily's crazy for them.
据说亚洲人新陈代谢比较快
Asian metabolism.
等她用那肮脏的小手去抓饼干的时候
When she grabs them with her grubby little hands,
触动机关
off goes the trap.
砰 一大滩牛奶
Boom--big puddle of milk.
她会有大麻烦的
She'll get in so much trouble.
我妈可讨厌一团乱了
My mom hates messes.
我知道克莱尔是什么样的人
I'm familiar with Claire.
准备
Lock...
待发
And loaded.
这饼干太好吃了
These cookies are so good...
又这么触手可及
And so easy to reach.
莉莉
Lily!
我的天呐 小卡
Oh, my god! Cam! Oh! Ohh!
怎么回事 你还好吧
What happened? Are you okay?
那盒牛奶 倒了 我肯定是踩滑了
Oh! That milk... Fell, and I must have slipped in it!
我又把牛奶忘在外边了吗 实在抱歉
Did I leave that out again? I'm so sorry!
我的背 哎哟 我的背
Oh! My back! Ooh! My back!
帮你做个瑞典式按摩好吗 口音您挑
Can I give you a Swedish massage, accent optional?
不用了 让我躺会儿就行
Oh! Oh, no, I just need to lie down.
来吧 我们扶你去沙发那儿歇歇
Come on. Let's just get you over to the sofa.
你觉得让闺女帮我踩背
Do you think it would be offensive
这个要求过分吗
if I asked our daughter to walk on my back?
有点 我刚刚不是说帮你按吗
I'd say so. I just offered to give you a massage.
不会吧 碧翠丝被你弄坏了
Oh, no! You broke Beatrice.
这下她没法喂海豚了
Now she can't feed the dolphins.
这孩子说什么呢
What is she talking about?
这是"甜蜜相伴"家的娃娃
Oh, it's a "My sweet companion" doll.
娃娃的背景故事都经过精心安排
They all have these elaborate backstories.
碧翠丝跟盲眼的海豚和模特是同事
Beatrice works with blind dolphins and models.
还有盲人模特吗
There are blind models?
真惨 都看不见自己有多漂亮
That's so sad. They cannot see how pretty they are.
好的 慢点 来吧
Okay. Hold on. Here we go.
扶稳了 扶稳了 扶稳了
Give me some. Give me some. Give me some. Oh!
我给莉莉买个新娃娃吧
Let me buy Lily a new doll.
小卡摔倒都是我的错
It's my fault Cam fell.
不用啦 "甜蜜相伴"店里
No, no need. Uh, the "My sweet companion" store
有个医院 里面有位值班医生
actually has a hospital with an on-call doctor.
我可以送她去 正好要带姑娘们去商场
Well, I can go. I'm taking the girls to the mall anyway.
那就太好了
Oh, that'd be great. Yeah.
别担心 娃娃有医保的
And don't worry. She has medical insurance.
我觉得咱今年应该达到免赔额了吧
Yeah, and I think we've met our deductible for the year,
所以应该不用花钱的
so you should be good.
没错
Yeah.
你们知道我们村里的娃娃啥样吗
Do you know what a doll is in my village?
叉子顶个苹果就算
An apple on a fork.
我都没玩过娃娃 这样很怪异吗
I never really got dolls. Does that make me weird?
绝对在"怪异名单"上
It's on the list.
你一点也不怪异
You're not weird.
你只是直接越过了小女孩阶段罢了
You just kind of skipped the little girl stage.
直接跳到"你敢按她门铃试试"阶段
And jumped to the "I dare you to ring her doorbell" stage.
您这辈子也就只有往钢管舞台上跳的命
The only stage you're ever going to jump on has a pole on it.
好歹我也有本钱啊
Hey, at least I have the body--
别吵 别吵
Okay! Okay!
我们要把这事移送法庭
We're gonna have to settle this dispute in court--
美食广场
The food court.
由尊敬的"肉桂卷"法官审理
The honorable judge Cinnabon presiding.
美食广场吗
The food court?
那地方一股卢克的自行车头盔味儿
That place smells like the inside of Luke's bicycle helmet.
-我喜欢美食广场 -我也喜欢
- I like the food court. - Me, too.
别担心 姑娘们 我们才不会因为
Don't worry, girls. We're not gonna deprive ourselves
海莉对食物无爱就亏待自己
just 'cause of Haley's aversion to food--
哦哦 你说无爱啊
Oh. Oh, Haley's "Aversion."
我还以为你说
I thought you said...
当我没说
Never mind.
好的 你打开电视之后
Okay, so after you have turned on the monitor
选择输入模式后
and selected your input,
就可以用这只换台了
you can change the channel with this guy.
但如果你要调节音量
But if you need to change the volume--
你知道吗 我觉得我这样挺好
You know what? I think I'm fine.
你忙你的去吧
Why don't you just go ahead?
我知道听起来很复杂
I know this sounds really confusing,
但我有个简单易上手的小诀窍
but there's actually a very simple way to remember it.
输入模式一是机顶盒
Input 1 is the cable box
-机顶盒 机 -我觉得我打个盹就好
- Cable box, ca-- - I think I'm just gonna take a nap.
那行 我去做瑜伽了
Okay. I'm going to yoga.
哇 听起来蛮有趣的啊
Ay! That sounds like so much fun.
你应该跟她一起去 歌洛莉亚
Oh, you should go with her, Gloria!
以后有机会一定会的
Oh, we should definitely do that sometime.
我会很乐意的 拜
I would love it. Bye!
看见她怎么用冷屁股贴我热脸了吧
Do you see how she gives me the cold shoulders?
我都不知道自己还试个什么劲
I don't even know why I try.
-抱歉 -这个 克莱尔就这德行啊
- Ay. Sorry. - Oh, well, that's just Claire, you know?
普里契特家人都那样
She's a Pritchett.
你得突破那层坚冰
You gotta break through those walls.
越早越好
The sooner the better.
你真这么觉得吗
You really think so?
没错 为什么不去呢 快走
Yeah. Why don't you go? Now.
搭建友谊的桥梁
Forge that friendship!
好 我去 我的健身包就在车里
Okay, I go. I have my gym bag in the car.
快好起来哦
Feel better!
好的 谢啦 我就趴在这儿
Okay, thank you! I'm just gonna lie here...
敷点冰块
Some ice on my back!
克莱尔根本没还我保鲜盒
I knew for a fact Claire never returned my Tupperware.
我只是需要点时间找找
I just needed a few minutes alone to find it.
等我找到
And when I did,
他们就再也不会偷笑了
I'd never have to hear them snicker again,
说什么"糊涂的小卡"或者"小卡忘性真大"
"Oh, silly Cam" or "forgetful Cam,"
因为君子报仇 十年不晚
because revenge is a dish best served cold.
而且更狠的是 两天后她就会发现
And even better, two days later
失去24盎司微波炉适用的
out of 24-ounce microwave-friendly
气密封口保鲜盒有多可怕
burp-sealed pak-n-stor.
嘿 我还以为你去药房了呢
Oh, hey! I thought you were going to the pharmacy.
忘带手机了
I forgot my phone.
我觉得我还在为跟我爸的那蠢事烦神
I think I'm just upset about this stupid thing with my dad.
亲爱的 我愿意听你娓娓道来
Well, sweetie, I'd love to hear about it
不过你得先帮我买暖宝宝去
when you come back with my heating pad from the pharmacy,
因为我背好疼 好吗
because I hurt my back, remember?
我说 他是不是反应过度了啊
I mean, did he overreact or what?
就是个游戏嘛 对吧
It's just a game, right?
除非有其他更深层次的意义
Well, unless there's something more to it.
或许你应该跟他谈谈
Maybe you should go talk to him.
或许吧
Yeah.
唉 早知道就不提那事了
Oh, I should have just kept my mouth shut.
那天多美好啊
I mean, it was such a great day.
在他以为自己一杆进洞后
After he thought he got that hole-in-one,
他带我们下馆子
he took us out to dinner.
给我买了人生中第一瓶啤酒
He bought me my first beer.
这不就对了 他也许就气在
Well, there you go. He's probably hurt
你毁了一段特殊的父子经历
because you marred a very special father-son experience.
-是吗 -你毁了它
- You think? - You marred it.
但你可以修补啊
But you can fix it.
他现在就在俱乐部呢
He's down at the club right now.
去吧 米奇尔
Go, Mitchell!
修补那段回忆
Un-mar that memory!
你知道吗 我要去
You know what? I'm gonna do it.
-疼 -抱歉
- Ow. - Sorry.
别担心 我马上就回来
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
好的 我会想你的
Okay! I'll miss you!
回来前打电话啊
Call first.
你当着他的面说那些话 有脑子吗你
What were you thinking saying that in front of him?
抱歉 说溜嘴了
I'm sorry. It slipped out.
况且 我觉得他早知道了
Besides, I figured he knew.
妈早知道了
Mom knows.
那也是她威逼利诱迪兰才知道的
Only because she dragged it out of Dylan.
而且她保证过在我上大学前不告诉老爸的
And she promised not to tell dad until I left for college,
也就是说本来可以一直瞒着他
Which means he might have never found out.
别慌了
Stop panicking.
我们都不确定他是否听清楚了我的话
We don't even know for sure he heard what I said.
好了 已经有护士在照顾碧翠丝了
Okay. Beatrice is with the nurse.
有事他们会叫我们的 应该不会太久
They'll call us. Shouldn't be too long.
我们等着吧 等到她结婚
We can just wait until she's married.
等到她准备好
Until she's... ready.
当然啦 现在的年轻人都是"时刻准备着"
Which, apparently, everyone is these days.
有意思的是
Funny,
我以为人家要到好几年后才会准备好呢
I used to think it'd be years until everyone was ready,
但我猜我错了 很傻很天真地错了
but I guess I was wrong. Wrong and naive.
惊喜哟
Surprise!
歌洛莉亚 天啊
Oh! Gloria. My god.
我来和你一起练瑜伽
I came to do yoga with you.
我真没想到你会来呢
I wasn't expecting to see you here.
对啊 所以我才会说惊喜哟
Yeah, that's why I say "Surprise!"
是啊 太不巧了 因为我刚刚想起来
Oh, yeah. This is awful, because I was just thinking
我好像得翘瑜伽课了
I might have to bail on yoga.
我突然间头痛的好厉害啊
I have the worst headache all of a sudden.
但是瑜伽对头痛很好啊 克莱尔
Oh, but yoga is good for that, Claire.
有冥想啊 还有那种哼哼叫啊
For the meditation, for the mmm...
是 是 只是现在
Yeah, yeah. It's just right now
我真的只想在漆黑的屋子里躺下来深呼吸
I wanna go lie down in a dark room and breathe.
听起来和瑜伽没什么区别嘛
That sounds like yoga.
这 这倒是
I... I realize that.
是没什么区别
Yes.
-但是 我得走了 -拜托
- But still, I-I... should go. - Come on.
人家才不要一个人上瑜伽课嘛
I'm not gonna do the class by myself.
那好 那我们去做个按摩吧
Okay, so let's go and get massages.
或者去这的一家美甲沙龙
or there's a nail salon there.
改天有时间的话我肯定特想去
Ooh, I would love to do that some other time,
我真的特想去 但是现在
I really would. But right now
我得回家躺着了 你能理解我 对吧
I need to get home and lie down. You understand, right?
-当然理解 -好的
- Of course. - Okay.
走吧
You go!
你就满嘴谎话吧
And lie.
你好了
You're better!
稍有起色 稍有
Barely. Barely, yeah.
我刚刚只是想拿点凉东西敷背
I was just getting something cold for my back.
拿肉汁敷
Gravy?
如果它能拯救你妈的火鸡
Well, if it can save your mom's turkey,
它就能治好所有东西
it can save anything.
你们不是要去见你朋友米兰达吗
I thought you were going to see your friend Miranda.
这货胆怯了
This one chickened out.
亏他还说自己非常喜欢女生
For someone who says he likes girls so much,
怕女生还差不多
he sure is afraid of them.
那可是要跟她跳舞啊 卢克
It's a dance, Luke.
懦夫舞吧
Chicken dance.
既然你们都回来了
Well, since you're back,
如果我给你们二十块钱
what if I give you 20 bucks,
你们俩
and you guys...
给我把车洗了怎么样
go wash my car?
是每人二十 还是总共二十
Is that 20 bucks for each of us, or both of us?
总共二十
Both.
我就知道他没那么大方
That's what I thought.
瞧瞧啊
Uh-oh, check it out.
"高手"又在盯着光荣榜呢
Ace is drooling over his plaque again.
抱歉 我还真没闻见你们几个二货进来
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't smell you idiots come in.
听着 我一直在想
Listen, I've been thinking,
或许还是别叫我"高手"了吧
maybe it's time we retire the name "Ace."
你是说你印在高尔夫球帽上的字吗
You mean the name you had printed on your golf cap?
-还有浴袍上 -其实 关于那个
- And his robe. - You know, guys, about that--
还记得我把他那帽子扯下来戴我头上
Remember how mad he got when I yanked that cap off his head
他怎么发飙的吗
and put it on?
你得自己赢取一顶光荣帽
You got to earn that!
是是是 我只是很庆幸
Yeah, yeah, well, I'm just glad
你那便宜的植发没卡进我帽子里
one of those cheap hair plugs didn't get caught in it.
说过多少次了 那不是植发
Hey, for the millionth time, they're not plugs.
那是啥 你头发在你五十岁时又回来了
So what, your hair just came back when you turned 50?
反正你老婆是没回来
Unlike your wife.
拜托 她不回来才好呢
Hey, that was a blessing.
否则 我今晚还约不了娜塔莉·霍布斯呢
Otherwise, I wouldn't be taking out Natalie Hobbes tonight.
出去吃饭还是帮人报税啊
Taking her out or doing her taxes?
我正想怎么澄清我那
So I'm trying to find a way to come clean
一杆进洞的囧事时 我突然间想
about the hole-in-one, when it occurs to me...
澄清毛啊
Why?
一个二货对他的性生活鬼话连篇
One idiot lies about his sex life,
另一个傻缺的法拉利都"在保养"N年了
the other dumbbell has a ferrari "In the shop" for years,
而三号二货是个好莱坞特技车手
and moron number three is a hollywood stunt car driver
而他却在倒高尔夫车时受伤了
who gets sick when he rides backwards in the golf cart.
那女士们准备好开球还是干嘛啊
So you ladies ready to tee off or what?
-我们付清酒钱就行动 -我付了
- Yeah, just gotta settle up our tab. - I took care of it.
你说你去洗手间的
You said you were going to the restroom.
这家伙真是没一句真话
Ah! Can't trust a word out of this guy's mouth.
都骗了我们二十年了
20 years we've been falling for this.
我 我抱歉打扰一下
I-I'm sorry to interrupt,
-但是我老爸从没骗过你们 -米奇尔
- but my dad never lied to you guys. - Mitchell...
直到今天他才知道
No, he didn't even know until today
-他从没打出一杆进洞 -这下可好
- that he never made the hole-in-one. - Okay.
但是事实上他知道真相后
But the fact that he couldn't live with himself
他受不了良心的责备
when he found out,
马不停蹄地过来向你们坦白
and he raced down here to confess to you,
这就足以说明他是个真男人
that just shows the kind of man he is.
他是个一杆进洞型的男人
He is a hole-in-one kind of man.
你从没打出一杆进洞
You never got a hole-in-one?
我还没坦白呢
I didn't tell them.
这么说 这就是你的兄弟帮哈
So this is the gang.
介绍介绍呗
Introduce me.
中奖了
Ahh. Score!
我和米兰达好像不是天生一对
It's not like me and Miranda are perfectly suited.
首先 她喜欢古惑仔类型
For one thing, she likes bad boys.
我又不是
That's just not me.
我要开音乐了
I'm gonna turn on some music.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
对女人温柔的本事我又甩不掉
I can't unlearn how to treat a lady.
最后又会怎么样呢
But where does that leave me?
等到了四十岁 她第一次离婚后
Waiting till I'm 40 when she looks me up on facebook
在Fackbook上找我吗
after a failed first marriage?
好啦
Okay.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我受够你对米兰达那些怨念了
I'm sick of hearing you whine about Miranda!
-现在去让她注意你 -但我们没办法
- It's time to make her notice you! - But we can't!
我们有一整箱汽油 她就住在街角
We got a full tank of gas, and she's right down the block.
系上安全带
Now buckle up!
-你疯了吗 -你说呢
- Are you crazy? - You tell me.
莉莉 这是什么
Lily, what is this?
化学仪器玩具套装不是更好吗
Wouldn't you rather have a chemistry set,
或是看图识字卡
or some flash cards?
她很漂亮
She's pretty.
不 她脏了
No, she's dirty.
来 把灰擦一擦
Look. Get the dirt.
我来把她擦干净
So let me wipe her off.
搞定
Fix that.
你的辫子松了 过来这儿
Your braid's coming loose. Come here.
立马搞定
Fix that right up.
我做了检查
So I completed the examination.
她情况还不错
She did really well.
诊断结果呢
What's the prognosis?
我们能大致修复手臂
We can fix most of her arm,
但她的肩关节无法完全恢复灵活度
but she'll never regain full mobility in her shoulder joint,
因为工厂不再生产那种零件了
because they don't make that part anymore.
挺不错的了 是吧
Well, that's pretty good, right?
至少看上去还是一样
I mean, she'll look exactly the same.
没人会知道
No one will know.
我知道
I'll know.
我只是喜欢她以前的模样
I'm just saying I liked her the way she was.
多可爱的甜心娃娃
She was such a sweet little doll.
对不起 医生
I'm sorry, doctor.
我有点适应问题
I'm having trouble adjusting to all this.
爸 她还是那个可爱的甜心娃娃
Uh, dad, she's still a sweet little doll.
不 她已经"破"了
No, she's broken.
不 她只是改变了一点
No, she's just changed a little.
生活就是这样 娃娃会长大的
It happens. Dolls grow up.
事实上
Well, actually--
-劳驾 -当然
- Uh, could you... - Yeah. Sure.
我正要去
I actually have to go
将噩耗告诉一个小女孩
give a little girl some pretty bad news.
海莉
So, Haley...
我想说的是...
The thing is...
其实 海莉已经快18了
Fact--Haley's almost 18.
其实 我是个酷老爸
Fact--I am the cool dad.
海莉 我理解性是生活的一部分
Haley, I understand that sex is a part of life.
虽然听到这个消息我并不开心
I can't say that I'm thrilled to hear this,
但我肯定你有注意"安全" 只要你乐意
but I'm sure you're being safe, and I hope that you'll feel free
随时都可以跟我谈论这个问题
to talk to me about this anytime.
我们应该
We should...
我们应该为碧翠丝打上
We should probably get Beatrice, like,
石膏什么的
a-a cast or something,
这样大家可以尽情涂鸦了
and we can all sign it. Yeah?
当然 当然
Uh, yeah. Sure.
其实 我说砸了
Fact--I blew it.
修复工作可能还要一阵
This repair's probably gonna take a little while.
你去美食广场给我们找张桌子
Why don't you run up to the food court and grab us a table?
我去接艾丽克斯和莉莉
I'll get Alex and Lily.
好的
Okay.
要吧台位还是卡座
Do you want the counter or a booth?
你觉得好就行
Whatever seems right to you.
我相信你
I trust you.
我有个酷老爸
I have a cool dad.
好 该你了
Okay. Your turn.
不行
Unh-unh! No way!
你到底要不要她注意你
Do you wanna get her attention, or not?
太赞了
That was amazing!
你看到米兰达的表情了吗
Did you see the look on Miranda's face?
没有 但你做得不错 西尔玛
No. But you did good, Thelma.
别这么叫我 我讨厌那电影
Please stop calling me that. I hate that movie.
什么电影
What movie?
天 到头了
Uh-oh! Dead end!
你得调个头
You gotta make a u-ey.
我不知道怎么做
I don't know how to do that.
她假装头疼 小卡
She pretended to have a headache, Cam.
她不想和我在一起
She doesn't want to spend time with me.
可能她只是想一个人待着
Maybe she just wanted to be alone.
为什么
Why?
因为有些人
Because some people
非常重视隐私
really value their privacy,
你必须得尊重这点
and you have to respect that.
我得挂了
I have to go.
好啊 克莱尔
Hola, Claire!
歌洛莉亚 你不能再这样了
Gloria, you've gotta stop doing that!
你想自己回去上瑜伽课 不带上我吗
Were you going back to the yoga class without me?
不 我不是因为这个回来的
No, that is not why I came back.
真搞不懂你
I don't understand you.
为什么你不想和我在一起
Why you don't want to spend time with me?
所有人都喜欢和我在一起
Everybody wants to spend time with me!
就连给我做指甲的女士
Even the lady that did my nails
都想带我去上普拉提课
wants to take me to pilates.
我不是回来上瑜伽课的
I didn't come back here to do yoga.
我不做瑜伽 只是个掩饰 好吗
I don't do yoga. It's a cover, okay?
听着
Look...
我知道在外人看来
I know that from the outside,
我生活美满 一切尽在掌握
it seems like I have everything together.
不 我没觉得啊
No, not really.
我想说我有时压力很大
My point is that my life can be very stressful.
我找了个放松的方式
And I have found a way to cope with that stress.
这是我的小秘密 我知道这不是什么光荣的事
And it's my little secret. And I'm not proud of it.
你好 克莱尔 里面见
Hey, Claire. See you inside.
你是在搞外遇吗
Is that what you do?
不 不是
No. No!
好吧 你跟我进来 来
Okay. You're coming with me. Come in.
但听着 歌洛莉亚
But listen to me. Gloria...
此事只能天知地知你知我知
It has to stay between us.
这儿是我的圣地
This is my sacred space.
浑身的压力都释放出来了
It's just such a great release.
-多谢你没用有色眼光看我 -怎么会呢
- Thank you for not judging me. - Why would I?
就算有 也是让我更喜欢你了
If anything, it makes me like you more.
你多久来一次
So how often do you come here?
也不是经常来
Not that often. No.
你好
Hey.
可能是有点小经常吧
Maybe a little often.
太可悲了
That's so sad.
我有仨孩子加一幼稚老公
I live with four teenagers.
你家连儿子都那么成熟
You live with two adults.
-你不了解 -不不 我说你可悲是因为
- You have no idea... - No, no, no. It's so sad
你经常来
that you come here so often
枪法就这水平
and that's the best that you can shoot.
指甲未剪 枪法也比你神勇
And that's with pretty nails.
但是姿势不对 我...
But improper stance. I...
-多练练吧 -好的
- Practice more. - Okay.
你的酒 "高手"
Here you go, Ace...
你真名叫什么
I mean... What is your real name?
杰
Jay.
-爸 -我说了 别提了
- Dad, I-- - I told you, forget about it.
好吧 我只想让你知道
All right. I-I just want you to know
我明白你为什么生气
I get why you're upset, okay?
你打出一杆进洞的那天
That--that day you got the hole-in-one,
对你来说意义重大
it meant a lot to you.
全被我破坏了
And... I... I marred it.
那天对我也有重大意义
But it meant a lot to me, too.
我们吃了牛排大餐 你让我喝了人生第一瓶啤酒
We had a steak dinner, you gave me my first beer,
而且
and, uh...
那是我们一起度过的非常美好的一天
It was one of the greatest days we ever spent together.
那天不应该是关于毫无意义的一杆进洞
And it wasn't about some meaningless hole-in-one,
而是我们的美好回忆
it was about us.
不 那天的意义就在于一杆进洞
No. It was about a hole-in-one.
是的 也许有一点关系吧
Yes. Yes. A-a little bit, maybe.
更重要的是 我们父子的感情加深了
But mostly, it was about how we bonded.
我以为我将球从球座击出
I thought I hit a ball straight from the tee
飞了很远很远
really, really far
进了一个小洞里
into a tiny hole.
好吧
Okay.
我又自讨没趣了
Well, when will I learn?
而且那不是你第一次喝啤酒
And it wasn't your first beer, anyway.
是的 爸 不过我也不指望你能记得
Yes, it was, dad, but I wouldn't expect you to remember.
你14岁生日时
It was your 14th birthday.
你想喝一口我的啤酒
You asked me for a sip of mine.
你妈当着你所有朋友的面吼你
Your mom yelled at you in front of all your friends,
说你还只是个小屁孩
said you were just a baby.
你含泪跑了出去
You ran outside in tears...
不幸的是 以事实证明你妈是对的
Which, unfortunately, supported your mom's argument.
总之 我拿着啤酒出去
Anyway, I came out with a couple of beers.
我们在门廊里喝的
We drank 'em on the porch
看着头上乌云袭来
watching the storm clouds coming in.
我完全忘记那事了
I had completely forgotten about that.
你真是不可思议
You know, you're-- you're unbelievable.
-就在我觉得你是...-风暴·史蒂文 没错
- Just when I peg you as some-- - Storm Stevens! That's it!
给我个可以写字的 我要马上写下来
Give me something. I'm gonna write it right here.
免得我忘记了 风暴·史蒂文
Before I forget. "Storm Stevens."
刚刚我们说什么来着
What were we just talking about? Just now?
没什么吗
No?
来吧 莉莉 去看看碧翠丝修好没
Come on, Lily. Let's see if Beatrice is ready.
爸
Hey, dad?
我知道自己已经不小了
I know I'm way too old for this,
可你能买这个娃娃给我吗
but do you think I could get this doll?
她叫吉纳薇
Her name's Genevieve,
她正在开发一种疫苗
and she's developing a vaccine for...
可以 我会买给你
Yes, you can get the doll.
你要多少我就买多少
You can get as many dolls as you want.
200块一个
It's $200.
一个就够了
Or one is fine.
我知道你就在这屋子里
I know you're here.
你们好呀
Hello.
我有个不好的预感
I have a bad feeling about this.
万一你的邻居看见了咱们怎么办
What if one of your neighbors saw us?
我们还是老实交待吧
Maybe we should just confess.
会的
We will...
二十年后
in 20 years.
什么
Huh?
你没听外公说吗 诉讼有时效的
You heard grandpa. There's a statute of limitations,
这可是件好事
Which is a good thing
因为我们还得把莉莉给灭了
because we still need to take Lily down.
算了 "萌娃宝座"给她吧
Nah, let her be the cute one.
我们不需要卖萌讨欢心了
We don't need that anymore.
咱现在是古惑仔了
We're bad boys now.
没错 这名号多响亮
Yeah. I like that.
古惑仔
Bad boys.
是你妈
Your mom!
天呐
Oh, my god.
小卡
Cam!
这个本来有盖的好吧
Um, this had a lid?
回见了 我去艾比家
I'll see you guys later. I'm going to Abby's.
拜 亲爱的 玩得开心点
Bye, honey. Have fun.
玩得开心点 和艾比一起
Have fun, you! With Abby!
确定有艾比这个人 而且是女生吗
We've confirmed Abby's a real person and a female?
是的 亲爱的 我们见过的
Yes, sweetie. We met her.
老公 不能因为我们知道了海莉的事
Honey, we can't treat Haley differently
就对她另眼相看
just because we both know what we know about her.
我知道 我只是需要些时间适应
I know. I just need time.
迪兰告诉你了
So Dylan told you?
他为什么不告诉我 我们以前可是无话不谈
Why didn't he tell me? He and I used to share everything.
别自寻烦恼了
You're upset about a lot of things.
好吧 我不再纠结就是了
Okay, I won't obsess over it.
我只想问一件事
I just wanna ask you one thing.
你知道这事多久了
How long have you known?
三个月
Three months.
我家大闺女发生了这么惊天动地的事
So this giant thing happened to our first born,
你却整整瞒了我三个月
and you kept me in the dark about it for three whole months?
抱歉 我只是不确定你能否接受
I'm sorry. I just wasn't sure how you'd--okay.
谢谢
Thank you.